dailyclik.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy - Dailyclik.com

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding that how we manage your personal information with respect to collect, use, disclosure and share personal information to assist Dailyclik website and to keep your information safe under privacy policy. The privacy policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice.

**Collection of personal information:** Dailyclik may collect your personal information such as name, company name, email address and demographic information such as age, income level, zip code and location. We may collect your information to tailor users experience on website that helps to filter content according to users’ preferences. We use these information to enrich users experience on website and give regular updates and promotional information to users. Additionally, we use third party company to collect non-personal information such as traffic on website, page view data, IP address, browser type and web log information to analyse use of website.

**Disclosure of Information:**

  1. Dailyclik keep your information confidential and will not share your information to external organization.
  2. In event of fraud or scam, Dailyclik reserves rights to disclose personal information to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offences. 
  3. We may be required information if respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other’s rights, or protects anyone’s rights, property or safety.
  4. We may share information to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf to detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services.
  5. We may transfer your personal data for internal business purposes.
  6. We will only keep your personal information up to an extent. in the event we sell our business to any third party, we will transfer your data and all assets to that third party for the purposes of continuing to provide the Services to you.

**Cookies and IP Address:**

A cookie is a small file containing information that is sent to your computer from a web server and stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookie allows that site to recognise your browser, user name, password, preferences and other information to provide rich website experience. We may track your IP address to identify your membership, demographic information, resolve problems with server, and administer the Site. We may use cookie to ensure same ad not to be seen repeatedly. We use third party ad companies to show ads on our website such ads contain cookies. Our third-party service providers may use cookies on the Website and we have no control or access cookies used by third- party service providers. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser. But it may affect on using website experience.

**Data Security:**

We have taken certain security to protect your personal information from misuse and alteration. We use some ways such as encryption, passwords, physical security to protect the security and integrity of your personal information. All member data and activity is stored separately and is not directly accessible through a web browser. We use many tools to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but as internet is not 100% secure so we make no guarantees. Hence, such information you will provide will be at on your own risk. You agree we have no liability in the event of theft, loss, alteration or misuse of personal or other information or Content, including, without limitation. Your registration is protected by a unique ID and password so we suggest don’t share such confidential information to anyone. By disclosing personal information online, you may receive unsolicited communication from other parties in return. Therefore, you should exercise caution and common sense in such disclosures.

**Modifying personal information and Email communication:**

You agree that we may use your information to contact you for customer service, to inform you of changes to any policy or additions to our site, advertisements, promotions or the services offered over our site. You may modify, review your personal information that you have provided us. Additionally, we may offer you subscription of newsletters and alerts after finding interest on website. You can opt-out email newsletter service by changing account setting. We will not change your preferences without your consent. 

**Changes to privacy policy:**

We reserve the rights to change privacy policy time to time, such changes will take effect from the date and time the revised Privacy Policy is available on the Site and will not reduce your rights under this policy without your explicit consent. If any change is made we will give your proper information via certain services such as email notification.

**Contact us:**

If you have any question or concern about this Privacy Policy don’t hesitate to contact us at: [info@dailyclik.com](mailto:info@dailyclik.com)

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post any new versions on this page.

We last updated our Privacy Policy on Janauary 01, 2013.
